{"data":[{"question":"It is earth's gravity that ________ people their weight.","a":"gives","b":"give","c":"giving","d":"given","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Simple present tense.\u00a0\n- That= gravity (singular)= give- gives.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"1"},{"question":"Generally speaking, people should have ________ as their desires will allow.","a":"much education","b":"as much education","c":"education","d":"for education","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Comparison of Equality: as + adj\/ adv+ as.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"1"},{"question":"A dolphin six ________ length can move as fast as most ships.","a":"foot in","b":"feet in","c":"foot of","d":"feet of","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Feet is plural of \"foot\".\n- Structure: number + measurement unit+ in length.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"1"},{"question":"With new technology, cameras can take pictures of underwater valleys ________ color.","a":"within","b":"for","c":"in","d":"by","answer":"3","explain":"\n- In (full) colour: a television programme, film, or photograph that is in colour contains colours such as red, green, and blue rather than just black and white.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"1"},{"question":"________ the fifth largest among the nine planets that make up our solar system.","a":"The Earth is","b":"The Earth being","c":"That the Earth is","d":"Being the Earth","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Simple present tense: S + V (normal Verb\/ to be) + O.\u00a0\n- \"That the Earth is\": That is unnecessary.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"1"},{"question":"In mathematics, a variable is a symbol ________ some element of a set.","a":"and representing","b":"represents","c":"that represents","d":"represents that","answer":"3","explain":"\n- That(pronoun): used as a subject of the relative clause\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"1"},{"question":"________ actress's life is in many ways unlike that of other women.","a":"An","b":"A","c":"As the","d":"That the","answer":"1","explain":"\n- An: used instead of a when the next word begins with a vowel sound","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"1"},{"question":"About 20 miles from Boston, ________ a little town named Concord that has a rich history.","a":"has","b":"there is","c":"there are","d":"where is","answer":"2","explain":"\n- There is + a\/ an + countable noun","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"1"},{"question":"An advisor to both Franklin Delano Roosevelt and Harry Truman, ________ of Bethune Cookman College.","a":"Dr. Mary Mcleod Bethune was the founder","b":"Dr. Mary Mcleod Bethune, who was the founder","c":"the founder was Dr. Mary Mcleod Bethune","d":"did the founder Dr. Mary Mcleod Bethune","answer":"1","explain":"\n- \"An advisor to both Franklin Delano Roosevelt and Harry Truman\" is an introductory phrases but doesn't have particular subject= right after comma we need a subject.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"1"},{"question":"Warmth, moisture, and oxygen are three necessary requirements ________ most seedlings.","a":"for cultivating","b":"for cultivate","c":"as cultivating","d":"can cultivate","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Sth is necessary for (doing) sth\/sth.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"1"}]}